What's up, Hernán?
Man, look, we wanted
to talk to you real quick.
We were thinking...
We like you...
-Say it.
-I am.
Here's the deal.
When are you leaving?
Speak properly, he'll think
we don't want him here.
No, I wanted to ask
if you sort of know
when you'll be leaving,
because it's been 4 months
since you've arrived...
You're scruffy-looking.
-A bit.
-Not a bit, a lot.
You leave poopy,
peed on underwear all over.
It's bad.
You steal gold, eat brunettes,
take our food...
Give me the fucking coconut!
-No, Anaya, give him the coconut.
-It's not his.
It's the beaners' coconuts.
Why don't you stay
in your own country?
They say the food we give them
is for pigs.
-It's cultural differences...
-Screw it, Vergantcutl!
Brother, brother, understand her.
She's irritated,
because her mom
is staying over for a few days
and we need the room,
it's family stuff.
Shut up, you suck up!
Listen, Spaniard,
didn't they say
they discovered India?
They discovered how to make
a fool of themselves.
Look, she's got a point.
Because when you got here,
you said you were only
taking a shower,
having something to eat,
ravage a woman or two,
but you didn't leave.
It's really cool, it was fun,
because we got to know
smallpox, mirrors,
the nits on the balls!
But all things
must come to an end, brother.
If you want me to leave,
give me something for the journey.
-Coconuts?
-No.
It could be gold,
precious stones, I don't know,
slaves, a piece of land.
No, get out.
Help me, brother,
because I ate a lot.
I'll be back with
the Tlaxcaltecs and the weapons.
-Cool.
-Such idiots!
-Why?
He doesn't know
Tlaxcal doesn't exist!
Good one!
S'up, man! Montezuma?
Did Cortés
really mess with you?
You were blown away
by this Sunshine thing
and that it's got
loads of hair.
I also have loads of hair,
check out down here.
-Wait.
-Enough, Monte! Monte?
-His boat is still there.
-Where?
There. And? If I make him
come back, you and I...
-Shall we dance on the mat?
-Could be.
Spaniard, wait,
don't go away! Wait!